

### **CONTACT ME**

- 501 297 401
- mar.bogucki@gmail.com
- S marbogucki
- in) marcin-bogucki-a96a8672

#### **LANGUAGES**

 English - B1 / good with reading and writing documentation

#### **HOBBIES**

- ⊙ Job-related Literature
- Sport gym, volleyball
- ⊙ Cinema Star Wars

# Marcin Bogucki

### Front-end Developer

A demanding job as a Front-end Developer will enable me to combine both my academic knowledge and practical skills. Willing to be a member of a professional team to improve job-related skills while gaining working experience, especially JavaScript and Angular JS.



## **EXPERIENCE**

2014-03 / today 2 years and 6 mths (Pruszkow)

DaVinci Medical System

Web Designer, Front-end Developer

Interfaces web application, preparation of HTML and CSS code for medical applications.

2013-04 / 2014-03 1 year (Gdansk)

Etendard Sp. zo.o.

Junior Front-end Developer

Website, online shops and web application (HTML adn CSS template creation).

2010-10 / 2013-03 2 years and 6 mths (Warsaw) Grupa Wsparcia Projektów Inwestycyjnych

Web Designer HTML/CSS Developer

Website design and building templates (HTML and CSS).

2010-06 / 2012-09 2 years and 4 mths (Warsaw) **Education Media House** 

XHTML/CSS Developer

Creating templates electronic diary for schools.

2008-09 / 2010-05 1 year and 9 mths (Warsaw) Go Studio

HTML/CSS Developer

Creating Website templates and online stores.



# **EDUCATION**

2016	0	info Share Academy Junior Front-end Developer Training	
2015 - 2016	0	English Unlimited B1 level	
2014	0	<b>Eduweb</b> Responsive Web Design	
2006-2007	0	Post-secondary school TEB Edukacja Graphic Designer	
2005-2008	0	University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn  Course in teaching and methodology, IT training qualifications	
2003-2008	0	University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn MSc Technical-Information Education	



# **SKILLS**

CIXILLO		SublimeText	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$
HTML	<b>••••</b>	WebStorm	<b>••</b> •••
CSS	$\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$	Visual Studio	<b>⊙</b> ○○○○○
JavaScript	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$	Photoshop	$\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$
jQuery	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$	Illustrator	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc$
SASS	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$	InDesign	$\odot$
PHP	<b>⊙</b> ○○○○○	JIRA	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc$
MySQL	$\odot$	Tortoise SVN	$\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$
Boostrap	$\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\bigcirc$ $\bigcirc$	GIT	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc$
RWD	$\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$ $\odot$	Scrum	$\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2015, item 2135 as amended